shakr.com 2014-07-04

# Privacy Policy - Shakr

Shakr Media ("Shakr") values the protection of your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes our current privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies to the Shakr.com site ("The Site").

The Site may contain links to related services and offerings, including vendor sites. These third parties may have their own privacy policies that can be viewed on their websites or by contacting these third parties directly. Since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of these third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

#### Information We Collect And How We Use It

We collect three different types of information. (1) Our web server logs, including information provided by Google Analytics, (2) Cookies and (3) information you explicitly provide to us through forms you fill out and files that you upload to our site.

#### Our Web Server Logs

When you visit any site on the internet, you always leave behind some sort of record of your virtual travels. Our site is no different. Some types of information that we collect, or that Google Analytics collects on our behalf, includes: Your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, the links you click on while visiting our site, the specific pages you view, your location, the name of your Internet Service Provider, web pages from which you link to our site, the date and time of your visit, web pages you go to from our site.

#### Cookies

We use cookies to make life easier for you. Cookies are the method we use to avoid requiring you to sign in each time you visit our site. If you prefer not to use cookies, you can disable them in your web browser settings.

#### Information You Provide

You provide certain information to us when creating an account, such as an email address and password. You also provide text that replaces default text in a video you are creating at Shakr, and files (photos, videos) that are used to customize Shakr videos. Shakr values your personal information and will not share this information with 3rd parties unless you explicitly choose to do so yourself. Please be aware, however, that video playback pages show all of the information you enter into a specific video, and anyone with the URL can view this information.

For quality assurance and to ensure that inappropriate content is not uploaded, Shakr employees may review your videos from time to time. At the beginning, we will review most if not all videos created by our users.

#### Children Privacy Policy

We take care to protect the privacy of children who use our services. Our policy is to avoid collecting personal information of children under the age of 13 pursuant to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act(COPPA).

#### Security of Information

Shakr will keep your personally identifiable information secure using methods deemed to be common and widely adopted in the industry. All of our employees have signed confidentiality agreements.

#### Changes to This Statement

Shakr may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will alert our users whenever such changes occur.

#### Contact Shakr with Privacy Concerns or Questions

If you have any questions related to privacy, please do not hesitate to contact us at privacy@sha.kr. You can also mail us at:

Shakr Media Seocho-daero 397 Suite 808 Seoul, Korea 137-070

Thank you.

_This document was last updated on May 22, 2013._
